[
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these <br> numbers: [1, 2, 3, 4, 5]?",
      "correctAnswer": "3",
      "options": [
        "2",
        "3",
        "4",
        "5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these <br> numbers: [2, 3, 4, 5, 6]?",
      "correctAnswer": "4",
      "options": [
        "3",
        "4",
        "5",
        "6"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these <br> numbers: [3, 4, 5, 6, 7]?",
      "correctAnswer": "5",
      "options": [
        "4",
        "5",
        "6",
        "7"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these <br> numbers: [4, 5, 6, 7, 8]?",
      "correctAnswer": "6",
      "options": [
        "5",
        "6",
        "7",
        "8"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these <br> numbers: [5, 6, 7, 8, 9]?",
      "correctAnswer": "7",
      "options": [
        "6",
        "7",
        "8",
        "9"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these <br> numbers: [6, 7, 8, 9, 10]?",
      "correctAnswer": "8",
      "options": [
        "7",
        "8",
        "9",
        "10"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these <br> numbers:> [7, 8, 9, 10, 11]?",
      "correctAnswer": "9",
      "options": [
        "8",
        "9",
        "10",
        "11"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these <br> numbers: [8, 9, 10, 11, 12]?",
      "correctAnswer": "10",
      "options": [
        "9",
        "10",
        "11",
        "12"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these <br> numbers: [9, 10, 11, 12, 13]?",
      "correctAnswer": "11",
      "options": [
        "10",
        "11",
        "12",
        "13"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mean of these <br> numbers: [10, 11, 12, 13, 14]?",
      "correctAnswer": "12",
      "options": [
        "11",
        "12",
        "13",
        "14"
      ]
    }
]